

MAHMOUD KASSEM

Software Developer

Contacts

+20-1000-2153-50

mahmoud.ali.kassem@gmail.com

Alexandria, Egypt.

LinkedIn: mahmoud-kassem

LinkedIn: mahkassem

Education

LICENSE / LAW Alexandria Univeristy 2006 – 2010

Skills

PHP – Laravel & C# – dotnet – NodeJS - NestJS

JS - Angular - React - Vue

Design - Photoshop

Prototyping - Adobe XD - Figma

Management – Git – Trello – Jira Zoom – MS Teams – Skype Slack

Profile

Highly skilled web developer. I got a set of experiences covering both front-end/back-end and DevOps frameworks and technologies. I like to be creative. I'm learning new technologies to fulfill my passion and to keep up-to-date with the market requirements.

Work Experience

Tech Lead

Alexandria For Programming / 2018 - Present

- Conduct daily and occasionally meetings with development team, designers, and project manager.
- Testing and inspecting quality of code.
- CI/CD using CircleCi.
- Performing Tests for new recruits.

Advanced Web Full Stack Mentor

Udacity / 2021 - Present

Full Stack Developer

GlobiSoft / 2016 - 2018

- Development of web sites/apps.
- Design Databases.
- Developing APIs for mobile and web apps.